So back to our test file,
let's duplicate this last test
and modify it accordingly. So we should return
404 if no rental
found for the customer
movie combination. So, in this test, to
simulate this edge case, we're going to deal with the
earlier. So we can simply call rental.
remove pass an empty query object,
clean up our rental collection. Now we execute our
request, and then assert that we get 404.
Save, back in the terminal, obviously we have
a failing test and let's double check that, we expect that
to get 404, but we got 401, beautiful.
So back in the production code, what is the simplest code that
we can write to make this test pass. Well, we need to find a
rental for this customer and movie. If that rental doesn't
exist, then we'll return a 404 error. So,
here we need to load our rental class, so on the top,
require, we go 1 level up,
to the models folder, load the module folder,
and then load the Rental class.
Now here, we call Rental.find
One. We could also use find, but find returns
an array. So then we'll have to look for the first element in an array.
So it's cleaner to use findOne
use a query object, now each rental has a
customer property which is an embedded document. So,
add a filter, we want to look for a rental with customer
with id equal to request
.body.customerId.
Okay? So, we use the .notation to access the
property in a sub document. Now similarly we need
another property here. So movie.
_id should equal request.body.
movieId. So, we await this
promise, to get the rental, now,
if it doesn't exist, we'll return
the response with status 404 with a message
like rental not found.
Save, back in the terminal, all tests
are passing. Beautiful. Now here's your next exercise.
I want you to write a test case and ensure that this endpoint returns
a 400 error, if this rental is already
processed. Which means, the return date is set. So
go ahead and you'll see my solution next.